Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.fourtee Mss.B.B61.inventory14
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents W
  - Warburg, Max M. (cont'd) (Box 94)
    - From Rosenblum, David, 1942 July 9
    - Enc. with Rosenblum, David, 1942 July 10
    - From Zollschan, T., 1933 Dec. 30
    - Enc. with Schneiderman, H., 1934 Feb. 13
  - Warburg, Nina L. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 14; 2p
  - Warburg, Paul M. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 10; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 May 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Sep. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Sep. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 June 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 May 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 1; 1p
    - From Heidgerd, D., 1931 June 4
  - Warburg, Paul M. Mars. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 4; 2p
  - Ward, Harry F. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Jan. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 7; 1p
      open letter
    - Found at end of Dec. 1941
      Enc. Statement of the President and Congress
    - To American Civil Liberties Union National Comm. and Board of Directors
      Enc. with Ward, Muriel
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 18; 4p
  - Ward, Henry B. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 24; 1p
    - From Roos, C. F., 1931 Nov. 14
  - Ward, H. J. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 5
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 7
  - Ward, Henry L. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 27
  - Ward, Hugh (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 10
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 7
  - Ward, Joseph Morris (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1896 Feb. 28
  - Ward, M. H. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 19
  - Ward, Muriel (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 18; 1p
  - Ward, William Hayes (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1906 June 2
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 15
    - To Boas, 1906 May 31
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 12
  - Warden, Salo D. (Box 94)
    - See Boas, F. Open Letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., 1938 Jan.
  - Ware, E. T. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1906 May 21
  - Waring, Bernard G. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 13
  - Warmburg, G. F. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1920 Feb. 20; 4p
  - Warmow, M. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1885 July 25
  - Warner, A. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 5; 2p
  - Warner, H. M. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1935 June 30; 2p
    - To Kaufmann, E. I., 1935 June 4; 1p
    - Enc. with Kaufmann, E. I., 1935 June 6
  - Warner, L. (Box 94)
    - From Malinowski, B., 1933 May 5
    - Enc. with Malinowski, B., 1933 May 5
  - Warnhuis, A. F. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 7; 1p
    - Enc. Boas, F. (to Westermann), 1925 Nov. 7
  - Warnshuis, A. L. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 15; 1p
  - Warren, Constance (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 24; 1p
    - To Holmes, 1936 Feb. 20; 2p
  - Warren, Lillie E. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1888 Nov. 13; 2p
  - Warren, W. R. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 4
  - Warrington, J. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 10
  - Warrington, M. R. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 26
  - Wartling (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 12; 2p
  - Wash, J. McL. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 22
  - Washburn, M. F. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 8
    - To Boas, 1931
    - See Boas, F. (to Woodworth, R.S.), 1931 Sep. 2
  - Washington, Booker T. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov. 30; 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 8
    - To Boas, 1904 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 22
    - To Boas, 1912 June 17
    - To Dr. Isadore Singer, 1907 Nov. 7
  - Washington Friends of Spanish Democracy (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1938 June 9; 1p
  - Washington Herald -- -Editor (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 23
  - Wasmuth, Günther (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 July 8; 1p
  - Wastl, J. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1932 Sep. 8; 2p
  - Waterman, G. O. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1908 June 16
  - Waterman, T. T. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 4; 9p
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 7
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 13
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 8
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 12
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 21
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 13
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 12
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 13
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 25
    - From Boas, 1917 May 7
    - From Boas, 1918 May 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 June 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 July 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 July 31; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 8; 1p
    - To Boas
    - Found at end of Dec. 1909
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 13; 4p
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 May 5
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 27
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 19
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 15
    - To Boas, 1913 July 23
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 30
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 16
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 5
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 27
    - To Boas, 1914 Aug. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Aug. 26
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1915 Aug. 18
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 2
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 17
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 May 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 May 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 July 7; 3p
    - To Boas, 1918 July 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 21; 3p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Sep. 14; 1p
    - Wrote from Guatemala, 1923 Sep. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Sep. 22; 1p
    - From Brooks, A. C., 1917 Apr. 12
  - Watkins, J. E. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 11
  - Watson, Blanche (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1924 Apr. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 10; 4p
  - Watson, Elizabeth (Box 94)
    - From Monroe, Paul, 1931 Nov. 20
    - Enc. originally with letter from Lucy A. Branham, 1932 Jan. 19
  - Watson, E. & C. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1925 May 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 19; 1p
    - From Gregory, W. K., 1931 Feb. 28
    - From Roos, C. F., 1931 May 20
    - Enc. with Roos, C.F., 1931 May 20
  - Watson, Goodwin (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 11; 2p
      See Boas, F. Paper on modern pop.
    - Found at end of July 1939
  - Watson, L. B. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1909 Sep. 23
  - Watson, Morris (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 22; 1p
  - Watson, R. J. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 22; 1p
  - Watts, Erhelbert (Box 94)
    - To Keppel, F. P., 1906 Aug. 13
  - Waugh, L. M. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1935 May 3; 1p
    - To Gies, W. J., 1918 Mar. 17; 1p
  - Waxman, Samuel (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 23
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 24
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 14; 2p
  - Wayman, Agnes (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 24; 1p
  - Weatherly, A. L. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1921 May 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 May 3; 1p
  - Weaver, Marjorie E. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 30; 1p
  - Weaver, W. (Box 94)
    - From Fackenthal, F. D., 1935 Apr. 10
    - Enc. with Fackenthal, F. D., 1935 Apr. 9
    - To Fackenthal, F. D., 1935 Apr. 9; 1p
    - Enc. Fackenthal, F. D. (to Weaver, W.), 1935 Apr. 10
  - Webb, W. P. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1915 Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 30
  - Webehay (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 9
  - Weber (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 3; 2p
  - Weber, Leonard (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1905 May 8; 1p
    - See Boas, F. (to Adams, E.D.), 1905 Nov. 1
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 10
    - To Boas, 1904 Apr. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1904 May 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 13; 1p
    - See margin: Jacobi, A., 1905 Feb. 22
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 28; 1p
    - Found at end of 1905, 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 12; 2p
    - Found at end of 1906, 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 1; 1p
  - Weber, Max (Box 94)
    - See Boas, F. (open letter), 1941 July 18
  - Weber, Rudolf (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1907 June 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 10; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 May 8
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 3
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1915 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1916 Sep. 29
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 21
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 19
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 9
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 16
    - From Boas, 1917 May 15
    - From Boas, 1917 May 19
    - From Boas, 1917 June 1
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 4
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1897 Mar. 17; 3p
    - To Boas, 1902 Aug. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 5; 4p
    - To Boas, 1904 Apr. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 June 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1910 July 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 22
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1913 July 14
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 19
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 19
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 7
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 18
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 25
    - To Boas, 1916 July 7
    - To Boas, 1916 July 12
    - To Boas, 1916 July 27
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 6
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 20
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 2
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 17
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 17
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 11
    - To Boas, 1917 May 4
    - To Boas, 1917 May 13
    - To Boas, 1917 May 27
    - To Boas, 1917 June 29
    - To Boas, 1917 June 29
    - To Boas, 1917 July 10
    - To Boas, 1917 July 25
    - To Boas, 1917 July 28
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 5
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 19
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 29; 3p
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sep. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 9; 2p
  - Webster, H. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1914 May 20
  - Weckbecker, W. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1926 May 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 May 12; 1p
  - Weeks, Alice S. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1920 May 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 6; 1p
  - Weeks, E. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 20; 1p
  - Weeks, L. J. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr, 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 26; 1p
  - Weeks, Raymond (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 18
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 23
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 16
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 24
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 27; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 20
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1920 May 13; 1p
  - Weel, J. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 4; 1p
  - Wehde, A. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 25; 1p
  - Wehle, Theodore (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 16; 1p
  - Weidenreich, F. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1934 May 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1934 May 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 May 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 May 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 July 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Aug. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Sep. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Sep. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Dec. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Aug. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 July 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Sep. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 3; 3p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 21; 6p
    - To Boas Enc., 1934 May 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 May 23; 4p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 July 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 Sep. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 17; 2p
  - Weidig, H. P. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 6; 1p
  - Weigand, Herman J. (Box 94)
    - To Prokosch E., 1936 Mar. 3; 1p
  - Weigner (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 22; 2p
  - Weil, A. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 22; 1p
  - Weil, Hermann (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 1; 1p
  - Weinauer, H. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 28; 4p
  - Weinberg, L. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1909 May 3
    - From Boas, 1909 May 6
    - From Boas, 1909 July 2
  - Weinberger, B. W. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 18; 1p
    - Written on Weinberger, H. (to Seligman, E.R.A.), 1927 Mar. 18
    - To Seligman, E.R.A., 1927 Mar. 18; 2p
  - Weinberger, Karl (Box 94)
    - See margin of Fredericks, Lillian, 1939 Jan. 20
  - Weinman, F. S. (Box 94)
    - To Jelenko, E.W., 1934 Feb. 2; 2p
  - Weinmann, Fritz (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 3; 1p
  - Weinreich, Max (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1938 July 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 13; 2p
  - Weinstein, Jacob J. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1934 Sep. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Sep. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Sep. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Sep. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Sep. 18; 1p
    - Enc. Heyman, David M. (to Weinstein, J. J.), 1934 Sep. 13
    - From Heyman, David M., 1934 Sep. 13
    - Enc. with Weinstein, J.J., 1934 Sep. 18
  - Weinstock, F. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1935 Sep. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Aug. 30; 2p
  - Weisbach, Auguste (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 5; 4p
    - To Boas, 1920 June 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 July 20; 3p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 May 1; 3p
  - Weisbach, Mrs. A. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 1; 1p
  - Weisberg, Benjamin (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 6; 2p
  - Weismann, Henry (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1914 Sep.; 1p
  - Weisner, Louis (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 26; 1p
  - Weiss, Dr. Hertha (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 21; 4p
  - Weissmann, H. (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1914 Sep. 18
  - Weitzner, Bella (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 27
    - To Bryan, Ruth, 1942 Apr. 20; 1p
  - Welborn, Irma (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 15; 2p
  - Welch, C. F. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 16; 1p
  - Welch, Marvin J. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1894 May 1
  - Welch, William Henry (Box 94)
    - From Boas, 1907 Sep. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 May 2; 1p
    - Enc. Boas, F. (to Jenks, J.W.), 1908 Mar. 23
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 27; 4p
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 23; 4p
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 27
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 June 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Sep. 27; 1p
    - See Boas, F. (to Wheeler, W.M.), 1933 May 23
    - From Boas, 1933 May 23
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Sep. 24
    - To Boas, 1908 May 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 27
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 2; 2p
  - Welch, W. W. (Box 94)
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 16
  - Welling, Richard (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 15; 1p
  - Wells (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 12
  - Wells, F. L. (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 30
    - To Dublin, L. I., 1935 Aug. 6; 1p
  - Welsh (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 15
  - Weltfish, Gene (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Mar. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 June 3; 1p
    - See Boas, F. (open Letter), 1941 Nov. 6
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 25; 1p
    - See Boas, F. (to Board of fellowships in the biological sciences), 1931 Jan. 1
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 19; 4p
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 July 4; 2p
    - See Fairchild, Mildred, 1938 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 5; 1p
    - From Benedict, R. F., 1929 June 11
  - Weltwitz, Mrs. F. (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 17; 2p
  - Wen, Guilie Nottmeyer (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1901 Jan. 28
  - Wendiner, H. G. (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 20; 2p
      Enc. notes on Cohan, H.
      notes on Gans, E.
    - see also K. G. Wendriner
  - Wendriner, Anna Hellersberg (Box 95)
    See Hellersberg-Wendriner, Anna
  - Wendriner, Dr. Karl Georg (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 July 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Aug. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 June 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 July 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 14; 3p
    - To Boas, 1934 July 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 July 22; 4p
    - To Boas, 1934 Sep. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 30; 3p
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 27; 3p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 June 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 July 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Aug. 10; 6p
    - To Boas, 1935 Sep. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 16; 3p
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 22; 4p
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 July 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 July 25; 3p
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 July 6; 4p
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 4; 4p
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 21; 4p
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 28; 3p
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 7; 1p
      Enc. Truger Deutscher Bildung
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 9; 2p
    - Enc. Barth, Dora und Hans (to Wendriner, K. G.), 1938 Dec. 19
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 16; 1p
    - See Seligmann, H. J., 1939 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1939 June 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 2; 4p
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 7; 4p
    - To Boas, 1939 Sep. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 4; 1p
    - See Enc. Price, Lawrence M., 1940 Feb. 16
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 July 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 July 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 July 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1941 Apr. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 7; 1p
    - From Barth, Dora, 1938 Dec. 19
    - Enc. with Wendriner, K. G., 1939 Jan. 9
    - From Barth, Hans, 1938 Dec. 19
    - See Barth, Dora, 1938 Dec. 19
    - Enc. with Wendriner, K. G., 1939 Jan. 9
    - From Hueusch, B. W., 1941 Apr. 29
    - From Martinus, Nijhoff, 1935 Dec. 14; 1p
    - To Jacobs, Miss, 1935 Aug. 9; 2p
    - ?, 1935 June 20; 2p
  - Wendt, R. L. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1928 Sep. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Sep. 25; 1p
  - Wendte, C. W. (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 9
  - Wenle (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 7
    - To Boas, 1913 June 26
    - To Boas, 1913 June 26
  - Wenner, G. U. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 13; 1p
  - Wensley, Richard (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 17; 1p
  - Wensley, Mrs. Richard (Maude B.) (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 4; 2p
  - Weraba, L. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 28; 1p
  - Werber, Bertha (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 10; 3p
      See Wolf, Bertha
  - Werfent, J. M. (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 11
  - Werkmeister (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 22; 2p
  - Werner (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 20; 4p
  - Werner, Adolph (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 12; 1p
  - Werner, Julius O. (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 15; 1p
  - Wertheimer, Bertha H. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1928 June 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 May 24; 2p
  - Wertheimer, M. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 6; 1p
    - To Boas
    - Found at end of Dec. 1935, 1p
  - Weseliska (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1899 June 12
  - Wesle, C. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 14; 3p
  - Wessel, B. B. (Mrs. M. J.) (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 May 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 3; 4p
    - Enc. Brief summary of research work on racial forces in community life., 1925 Mar. 5; 2p
    - Enc. Wessel, B.B. (to Day), 1925 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 May 5; 1p
  - West, C. J. (Box 95)
    - To Fackenthal, F. D., 1935 May 27; 1p
  - West, Gerald M. (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1894 May 21
    - To Boas, 1894 May 22
    - To Boas, 1894 May 26
    - To Boas, 1894 June 4
    - To Boas, 1894 June 13
    - To Boas, 1894 July 11
    - To Boas, 1894 July 13
    - To Boas, 1894 July 26
    - To Boas, 1894 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, 1895 Jan. 1
    - To Boas, 1895 Nov. 28
    - To Boas, 1895 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1895 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1895 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1896 Jan. 22
    - To Boas, 1896 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, 1896 May 20
    - To Boas, 1896 June 22
    - To Boas, 1897 Mar. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1896 July 21
  - West, Phebe (Box 95)
    - To Gordon, Paul W., 1933 Sep. 4
    - Attached to letter from Gordon, Paul (to Boas, F.), 1933 Oct. 4